<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>FanLine</title>
 <link href="http://www.thefanline.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://www.thefanline.com/"/>
 <updated>2014-02-13T23:17:34-08:00</updated>
 <id>http://www.thefanline.com</id>
 <author>
   <name></name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>A Week of Firsts</title>
   <link href="http://www.thefanline.com/2014/02/10/A-Week-Of-Firsts/"/>
   <updated>2014-02-10T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.thefanline.com/2014/02/10/A-Week-Of-Firsts</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h3&gt;SMU&amp;#39;s Climb&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a week of many firsts, in college basketball as well as for us at FanLine. This week, Southern Methodist (SMU) climbed in the Top 25 for the first time in 3 decades. If you are wondering why this is newsworthy, SMU is coached by a person who is in the Basketball Hall of Fame and is the only head coach in history to win both a NCAA and NBA Championship. He is also the only coach in history to have taken 8 different NBA teams to playoffs! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!--more--&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;Can you guess who? Answer at the end of the newsletter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For us at FanLine, we advertised on Facebook for the first time and also posted flyers in college campuses. Many FanLiners have also been spreading the word and asking their friends to sign up – we greatly appreciate your support, thank you. More FanLiners from your school means better the chance your school has of winning scholarship funds, so please keep the referrals going.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Leaderboard Status&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking into account games played as of Sunday, we have a different school leading each of the 3 leaderboards. Purdue continues to lead the Most Knowledgeable Fanbase leaderboard, Venki (Auburn) leads the Most Accurate Fans leaderboard but needs 7 more solid games to be eligible for consideration. We now have a new leader in the Most Passionate Fans leaderboard with Jeanmz, leading a Cal 1, 2 standing on that leaderboard. New FanLiners are joining each day and we look forward to an intensifying fight for the top spot this week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are wondering how well you did in a single game, you can check it out &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thefanline.com/predictedgames&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;This week’s games posted&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All games for this week are now open for prediction. We will be treated to some great in-state rivalry games this week – Kansas vs. Kansas State, Duke vs. North Carolina, IU vs. Purdue and Arizona vs. Arizona State to name a few. If you have been following college basketball for some time, you know that ranking doesn&amp;#39;t matter when it comes to rivalry games. Passion and emotion takes over and rivalry games regularly feature upsets. Keep that tip in the back of your mind when predicting this week’s games at FanLine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, we would greatly appreciate if you can continue to spread the word about FanLine. Like us on Facebook and more importantly ask you friends to join you at FanLine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In case you are wondering about the SMU Head Coach, it is Larry Brown.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>A Week of Upsets, New Faces on the Leaderboard</title>
   <link href="http://www.thefanline.com/2014/02/03/A-Week-Of-Upsets/"/>
   <updated>2014-02-03T00:00:00-08:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.thefanline.com/2014/02/03/A-Week-Of-Upsets</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h3&gt;Super Bowl Voodoo and A String of Upsets&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s been a week for fans of underdog schools to feel great headlined by Cal upsetting the No.1 team in the country. Other notable upsets preceded and followed Cal&amp;#39;s upset; Kansas lost to Texas, MSU to Georgetown, Michigan to IU, Wisconsin to OSU, Pitt to Virginia, OK State to Baylor, UMass to St. Josephs and Memphis to SMU. Probably we can attribute all the upsets to Super Bowl! This year, 4 Top 10 teams lost the day before the Superbowl and you know what, the exact same thing happened last year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Probably FanLiners were aware of this stat since most of you did a great job in correctly calling the upsets! In fact, 65% of Fanliners who predicted the Cal vs. Arizona game called it right! Maybe Vegas should look at the collective prediction made by FanLiners before setting the lines for games!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Leaderboard Status&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of Sunday, &lt;em&gt;Purdue&lt;/em&gt; is leading in two leaderboards and &lt;em&gt;Auburn&lt;/em&gt; in the other. The hardest leaderboard is the Most Accurate Fans leaderboard and even though Fanliner &lt;em&gt;Venki&lt;/em&gt; still retains the No.1 spot, Fanliners &lt;em&gt;kdex&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;BearTerritory&lt;/em&gt; have done very well by scoring above 50 with their first submission – looks like they are ready to challenge the players above them this week.  We are sure other new Fanliners are just warming up as well.  Looking forward to more excitement this week. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Btw, if you ever wondered how well you did in a single game, you can check it out &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thefanline.com/predictedgames&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;This week’s games posted&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All games for this week are now open for prediction. There are a lot of Top 25 and other interesting games this week (Stanford vs. Cal, Uconn vs. Cincinnati, Michigan vs. Iowa, MSU vs. Wisconsin, to name a few) and we look forward to seeing how FanLiners do in some of these games. Just go to &lt;a href=&quot;www.thefanline.com&quot;&gt;FanLine&lt;/a&gt; and start predicting (and let&amp;#39;s keep beating Vegas!). &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
